cancanit.com 2013-06-06

# Cancanit.com - Privacy Policy

## INFORMATION COLLECTION AND PRIVACY POLICY

This information collection and privacy policy represents how the information from http://www.cancanit.com site (the "Site") is gotten and controls the information you give us. Your entries to the Site are not controlled and the policy doesn`t edits you submit to the Site. That information is dealt with singly at this link Terms and Conditions of Use. Right after posting on the Site any changed and revised information collection and privacy policy comes into force.

If there are some questions concerning this statement, you can contact cancanit.com or send mail to Website Administrator (the mail is at the bottom of this page). We will try to respond to every inquiry but it may take some time due to the large amount of inquiries we receive.

Cancanit uses information concerning websites from the public "whois" databases. Also the information is received from other public sources and from the "about us" section of websites. After that the information is made available, together with a link to the websites, screenshots, and logos one centralized place of the Site. Also everybody can build a map that is some kind of a spatial representation of otherwise public information. This map can be made by using the "about us" tool and one of innumerable free web mapping applications available in the Internet. The information that is available from the Site is only the information which is publicly available. We can also make available contact information for a website so users may freely edit and add data concerning websites.

If you don`t wish our bot to collect information about your website just follow the instructions on the Cancanit: Bot page.

### Control of User Provided/Edited Posts:

Cancanit users can freely edit entries. The identity of any user who provides information or make edits is not controlled. Due to an "Owner Contributed Information" feature you as the owner of a website can control the basic information about that website. You should control this information by yourself before relying on it.

### Cancanit Respects Intellectual Property Rights:

Cancanit respects the intellectual property rights of third parties. Copyright or trademark violation is forbidden. Cancanit provides free information concerning domain names and related websites. We publish texts or images from a site just to provide information about the site itself. Without watching the information from the site we can`t provide full information about that site.

The information that Cancanit gives may not be entitled to copyright defense in the first instance. Presents of smaller thumbnail-size images and of public text falls under "fair use". Fair use is a doctrine in United States copyright law that allows limited use of copyrighted material without requiring permission from the rights holders, such as for commentary, criticism, news reporting, research, teaching or scholarship. It provides for the legal, non-licensed citation or incorporation of copyrighted material in another author's work under a four-factor balancing test. According to this test, Cancanit`s use refers to fair use. Cancanit has gathered this information in a single place to provide knowledge about domain names and websites that is free to be editing by the user.

Cancanit presents the text and images in order to inform users about the domain names and website where the complete text and full images may be found. It doesn`t include the expressive value of text or images. Cancanit doesn`t harm the market by using this data. We only raise potential exposure for your website by presenting this information. According to this Cancanit`s use of the information applies to the fair use test. You can find additional information and discussion about Cancanit`s position on fair use and intellectual property policy at Intellectual Property Policy.

If you don`t want to present information from your site, please read the above instructions.

### What Information We Gather And How We Use This Information:

You can visit most parts of the Site without opening any Personally Identifiable Information ("PII") about yourself and we also don`t gather any PII about users from the Site. Only if you provide it to us by yourself. But if you place or edit any information available on the Site we log your Internet Protocol (IP) address. So this information will be showed together with the edited information and is publicly available. Your IP address can be used by the third parties to know more information about you.

a) Your Log-in/Registration Information. If you want to log-in to use the Site, you may be required to provide PII. Part of this log-in information will be showed together with the content you provide to the Site. Otherwise, any data that you give as part of registration or log-in won`t be passed to anyone unless it will be allowed by this privacy policy and will be used only for the purpose for which you give that information.

b) Information Tracked by Cookies. When your use our Site we may send a Cookie to your browser in order to help us to track and compile your browsing habits on the Site. How We Use This Information: The Cookies are in order to control whether you are a registered person and to observe your visits to the Site. Also the Cookies are used to know the amount of visitors coming to the Site. We don`t use your cookies or usage paths to identify you. We use the amount of your Cookies to determine usage paths and confirm them with any demographic data you provide. We can also use Cookies for special advertisements to you on the Site due to your browsing habits. Most of the browsers includes the function to disable Cookies. But this may cause not proper work of some of our services.

c) Information Tracked by Web Beacons. In purpose to know if you read our email we can send you Web Beacons concerning e-mails. Besides we use them to observe your browsing habits on the Site. We also use Web Beacons to watch and control the efficiency of certain communications and the efficiency of our marketing campaigns. We can also use Web Beacons for special advertisements to you on the Site due to your browsing habits tracked by them.

d) Non-Personally Identifiable Information or Aggregated PII. The information received from server logs, Cookies and Web Beacons won`t be used for your identifying until it will be requested by law or subpoena, or until it will be necessary to defend the security or rights of Cancanit, its customers, employees or property. Also we may collect PII and make statistics based on it, but it won`t identify you personally. How We Use This Information: Cancanit can make available non-Personally Identifiable Information or collected PII to third parties in propose to define the results of a promotion, event or third party relationship. Also to transfer data to current or potential customers, or to enlarge your online experience.

### Data Other Companies and Advertisers Gather: 

a) Sites We Do Not Own or Operate. We can transfer links to third party websites which are owned or operated by other companies that are not controlled by us. Please note, that this websites can gather data about you, but we can`t control their data collection. All data concerning data collection and usage is written in the privacy policy of that website.

b) Advertisers. Cancanit can place advertising on the Site. You should that know you don`t have to provide the PII to a third party. Remember it when you visit any site shown in an advertisement. Before providing PII you should carefully examine privacy policies and practices of the advertiser because they can be different from those of Cancanit. Also advertising partners of a third party may use cookies on the sites that allow them to observe a user's cookie during his visit to their sites.

### Revisions to This Policy: 

a) Please note, that we promise to post notice on our Site in order to inform you about any material revisions or changes in our privacy. Unless you personally contact us about your data it will be controlled by the current policy.

b) Assignment of Data. Cancanit can be involved in a transaction such as a sale, integration, or a transfer of all of our assets. This may require to assign any of the data controlled by this privacy policy. In such way it may cause the assignment or transfer of your data to a third party also with PII.

### Children's Privacy: 

NOTE: Cancanit.com and its services may not be used by children under the age of 18 without the advance written approve of a parent or legal guardian. Cancanit doesn`t collect data from children under the age of 18 and does not grant its services, software and the Site to children under 18. The Parental Consent Form can be found here.

Also note that Using any part of this Site you agree with the terms in this privacy policy.

### Privacy Policy -- Glossary of Terms

"Cookies" are small files which are stored on a user's computer. They are designed to hold a modest amount of data specific to a particular client and website

"Personally Identifiable Information" or "Personal Information" or "PII" refers to information that can be used to uniquely identify, contact, or locate a single person or can be used with other sources to uniquely identify a single individual (name, address, phone number or other data that can personally identify you).

"Web Beacons" is an object in a web page or e-mail and is usually invisible to the user but allows checking that a user has viewed the page or e-mail.
